https://www.esolarenergynews.com/p/privacy-policy.html

eSolarEnergyNews.com Privacy Policy
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your email address or other details to help you with your experience.
When do we collect information?
We collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on our site.
Provide us with feedback on our products or services
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
• To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
• To improve our website in order to better serve you.
• To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
• To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.
How do we protect your information?
Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.
We use regular Malware Scanning.
We do not use an SSL certificate
• We do not need an SSL because:
Only transactions are done via Paypal
Do we use 'cookies'?
We do not use cookies for tracking purposes
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.
However, you will still be able to place orders .
Third-party disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third-party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Google
Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en
We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.
Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.
We have implemented the following:
• Google Display Network Impression Reporting
We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.
Opting out:
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.
California Online Privacy Protection Act
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf
According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:
Users can visit our site anonymously.
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.
You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:
• On our Privacy Policy Page
Can change your personal information:
• By emailing us
How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?
We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.
Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?
It's also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.
We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.
Fair Information Practices
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:
We will notify the users via in-site notification
• Within 7 business days
We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
CAN SPAM Act
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.
We collect your email address in order to:
• Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions
• Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.
• Send you additional information related to your product and/or service
• Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.
To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:
• Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
• Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
• Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
• Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
• Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
• Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at
• Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.
and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.
eSolarEnergyNews.com
738 SW K St.
No comments:
Post a Comment
Home
Subscribe to:
Posts (Atom)
Aug 2019 (2)
Jul 2019 (1)
Sep 2018 (1)
Nov 2017 (1)
Sep 2017 (2)
Aug 2017 (1)
Jul 2017 (2)
Jun 2017 (2)
Apr 2017 (10)
Mar 2017 (22)
Feb 2017 (27)
Jan 2017 (21)
Dec 2016 (12)
Nov 2016 (13)
Oct 2016 (11)
Sep 2016 (22)
Aug 2016 (35)
Jul 2016 (7)
Jun 2016 (9)
May 2016 (6)
Apr 2016 (3)
Mar 2016 (20)
Feb 2016 (34)
Jan 2016 (8)
Nov 2015 (2)
Oct 2015 (7)
Sep 2015 (6)
Aug 2015 (7)
Jul 2015 (28)
Jun 2015 (23)
May 2015 (35)
Apr 2015 (19)
Mar 2015 (25)
Feb 2015 (31)
Jan 2015 (30)
Dec 2014 (19)
Nov 2014 (40)
Oct 2014 (60)
Sep 2014 (33)
Aug 2014 (26)
Jul 2014 (39)
Jun 2014 (40)
May 2014 (36)
Apr 2014 (48)
Mar 2014 (66)
Feb 2014 (57)
Jan 2014 (48)
Dec 2013 (27)
Nov 2013 (33)
Oct 2013 (24)
Sep 2013 (26)
Aug 2013 (82)
Jul 2013 (63)
Jun 2013 (71)
May 2013 (106)
Apr 2013 (73)
Mar 2013 (122)
Feb 2013 (136)
Jan 2013 (124)
Dec 2012 (92)
Nov 2012 (104)
Oct 2012 (124)
Sep 2012 (103)
Aug 2012 (132)
Jul 2012 (136)
Jun 2012 (159)
May 2012 (220)
Apr 2012 (164)
Mar 2012 (204)
Feb 2012 (205)
Jan 2012 (180)
Dec 2011 (87)
Nov 2011 (188)
Oct 2011 (206)
Sep 2011 (157)
Aug 2011 (194)
Jul 2011 (166)
Jun 2011 (147)
May 2011 (157)
Apr 2011 (96)
Mar 2011 (147)
Feb 2011 (147)
Jan 2011 (164)
Dec 2010 (139)
Nov 2010 (181)
Oct 2010 (204)
Sep 2010 (91)
Aug 2010 (123)
Jul 2010 (191)
Jun 2010 (108)
May 2010 (131)
Apr 2010 (64)
Mar 2010 (155)
Feb 2010 (38)
Jan 2010 (46)
Dec 2009 (82)
Nov 2009 (92)
Oct 2009 (146)
Sep 2009 (126)
Aug 2009 (73)
Jul 2009 (122)
Jun 2009 (111)
May 2009 (155)
Apr 2009 (146)
Mar 2009 (137)
Feb 2009 (108)
Jan 2009 (54)
Dec 2008 (28)
Nov 2008 (22)
Oct 2008 (33)
Sep 2008 (32)
Aug 2008 (28)
Jul 2008 (35)
Jun 2008 (29)
May 2008 (58)
Apr 2008 (34)
Mar 2008 (47)
Feb 2008 (21)
Jan 2008 (36)
Dec 2007 (15)
Nov 2007 (16)
Oct 2007 (4)
Aug 2007 (2)
Jul 2007 (2)
Jun 2007 (12)
May 2007 (14)
Apr 2007 (8)
Mar 2007 (6)
Feb 2007 (12)
Jan 2007 (1)
Dec 2006 (5)
Nov 2006 (4)
Oct 2006 (7)
Sep 2006 (14)
Aug 2006 (4)
Jun 2006 (4)
May 2006 (20)
ROY, MI.--( eSolarEnergyNews )--LG Chem Ltd., a global leader in lithium-ion batteries for automotive, stationary and consumer application...
Internet of Things Includes the Ocean, and it's Solar Powered
SAN DIEGO, CA--(eSolarEnergyNews)--Kyocera’s solar panels, tested for long-term deployment in marine and coastal areas, are powering an inno...
IKEA Taps Phoenix Solar for Rooftop Solar Project in Singapore
SINGAPORE & SULZEMOOS, GERMANY --(eSolarEnergyNews)--Singapore’s Phoenix Solar Pte Ltd has been awarded a contract by IKEA Southeast Asi...
IKEA Installs the Largest Rooftop Solar in Memphis,Tennessee
MEMPHIS, TN--( eSolarEnergyNews )--IKEA, the world’s leading home furnishings retailer, today announced that solar panel installation is com...
IKEA to Install Washington’s Largest Rooftop Solar Array in Renton, WA
RENTON, WA.--(eSolarEnergyNews)--IKEA, the world’s leading home furnishings retailer, today announced plans to install solar panels atop t...
Colorado Fires up Latest Solar Power Project
WELLINGTON, CO --( eSolarEnergyNew s)-- PSEG Solar Source, Platte River Power Authority and juwi today joined to dedicate the PSEG Rawhide F...
Sunnova and PetersenDean Partner to Deliver Integrated Solar Solutions to California Homebuilders
HOUSTON, TX--( eSolarEnergyNews )--Sunnova Energy International Inc. (NYSE: NOVA), one of the leading U.S. residential solar and battery sto...
The Connection Between Solar and Bitcoin
The fall of installation costs is one of the main factors driving the solar energy boom. One key indicator of this extraordinary growth is t...
Amazon Meets Solar Goals Quicker Than Expected
SEATTLE, WA--( eSolarEnergyNews )--Amazon
today announced the early completion of its
commitment to host 50 solar
systems on its fulfill...
Apple Announces Environmental Progress in China & Applauds Supplier Commitment to Clean Energy
BEIJING, CHINA--(eSolarEnergyNews)-- Apple®
today announced a significant commitment by major supplier Lens Technology to run its Apple ope...
